# MUHAMMAD SADAM MAHENDRA

## **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER**

085156321345 | sadam.mahendra@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/m-sadam-m | https://sadammahendra.netlify.app/

Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Fresh graduate of Information Technology from Darma Persada University. Experience of participating in the Independent Study "Kampus Merdeka" on Front-End Web Developer and React, and completing a Fullstack Developer bootchamp at Harisenin, makes me have interpersonal and communication skills, as well as good knowledge related to software development. I am a passionate and hardworking person, always working effectively with attention to detail, and also have a high motivation to succeed and always enthusiastic in learning new things.

# Work Experience

### PT. Presentologics - Bandung, Jawa Barat

Aug, 2022 - Dec, 2022

Front-End and React Web Developer independent study

- Modified software applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript based on specifications.
- Managed code in a Github repository and collaborated with other developers.
- Developed React web apps that utilize functional components, stateful components, and controlled components well. Apply property validation, routing, component lifecycle, context, and hooks well.
- Designed a final capstone project, in terms of application/solution development. Won the award for the best team in the Capstone Project.

## **Project Experiences**

Chefmate Web - Harisenin Project

Feb, 2024 - July, 2024

- Developing a Recipe website as Chefmate with the team.
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React.js
- Back-End : Mysql, Node.js, Express.js, and Sequelize

Smile App Web - Dicoding Project

Aug, 2022 - Dec, 2022

Front-End and React Web Developer

- Developing a parent website as a smile app using HTML, CSS, Javascript and react js with the team.
- Creating a smile app website for the final capstone project.

Library Web - Intern Project

Mar, 2022 - Jul, 2022

Full-Stack Developer

Contribute to creating a web library at SMPN 52 Bekasi City using the php programming language.

### **Education Level**

### Darma Persada University - Jakarta, Indonesia

2019 - 2023

Bachelor Degree of Informatics Engineering, 3.67/4.00

- Thesis Sentiment Analysis of Customer Satisfaction Levels Towards J&T Express Courier Services Using Support Vector Machine (SVM) Algorithm Based on User Reviews on Google PlayStore.
- Relevant Course Works: Database, Web Development and Python.

## Courses, Training and Certifications

Harisenin.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Feb, 2024 - July, 2024

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for recipe as a chefmate, within six months
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Js, mysql, node.js, express.js, and Squelize
- · Certificate:
  - bit.ly/sertifikat-kelulusan-harisenin
  - bit.ly/sertifikat-highest-achievers

## Dicoding Indonesia - Bandung, Jawa Barat

Aug, 2023 - Dec, 2022

Front-End and React Web Developer

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for parenting as a smile app, within five months.
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React Js.
- Certificate:
  - bit.lv/Sertifikat-Best-Caption
  - bit.ly/Sertifikat-Kelulusan-dicoding

# Skills

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Js, Bootstrap, Node.js, Mysql, Express.js, Sequelize, Python, PHP, GitHub.

Soft skills: Problem Solving, Time Management, Analytical Thinking and Teamwork

Languages: Indonesian (Native), English (Beginner)